https://www.legalmann.com/privacy-policy/

We are taking the threat of COVID-19 very seriously. Learn More.Call Me. Let's talk about your case(702) 474-6266Our FirmTypes of Criminal CasesCase ResultsReviewsContact Us
(702) 474-6266 Request a Callback
Do you need a Las Vegas criminal defense lawyer? Joel will fight for you.
(702) 474-6266 Request a Callback
Do you need a Las Vegas criminal defense lawyer? Joel will fight for you.
Get Your FreeConsultation:RequiredRequiredSend Now
Home Privacy
The Law Office of Joel M. Mann Privacy Policy Law Office of Joel M. Mann thanks you for visiting this web site. Law Office of Joel M. Mann is committed to protecting your privacy while providing you with a positive on-line experience. Law Office of Joel M. Mann respects your privacy, and we believe you have the right to know what information we collect, how we use it and what security measures we have taken to protect your information.
Table of Contents
hide
1 Collection and Use of Information
2 Providing Information to Outside Parties
3 Security
4 Updates and Removing Your Name
Collection and Use of InformationWhen you visit www.legalmann.com and use our Contact Form, certain information may be collected. Among the types of information that may be collected are:Domain names of visitors to our site;Your name, address, e-mail address and additional information you provide in the form;“Navigational information” regarding the traffic patterns of our site, including the number of visits to a particular page and user-specific information on which pages a guest visits, average length of time spent on the site and similar site usage data; andAny information that you may choose to submit in connection with any e-mail messages, on-site surveys, registry programs, contests and the like.Law Office of Joel M. Mann uses this information to help us develop and improve our site to better meet your needs. We may use your name or e-mail address to contact you or respond to your inquiries. We also use this information to help us diagnose technical issues relating to the performance of our website.Providing Information to Outside PartiesLaw Office of Joel M. Mann does not sell, trade, rent or otherwise provide your personal information to any outside parties.SecurityLaw Office of Joel M. Mann makes every effort to protect the security of your personal information. Any personal information you provide will not be stored on our server. Any information collected by us is stored in private files behind a firewall designed to protect your information by denying unauthorized access by outside users.Updates and Removing Your NameIf you do not wish to receive e-mails from the Law Office of Joel M. Mann in the future please let us know by contacting us.Meet Joel M. MannView Joel’s Full Profile »
Awards & Recognition
Contact Joel M. Mann. Call or click now! (702) 474-6266 Start Your Case Today
facebook twitter linked in youtube
HomeContact UsBlogSite MapDisclaimerPrivacy Policy
© 2020 Law Office of Joel M. Mann. All Rights Reserved.
Site by Consultwebs.com: Law Firm Website Designers / Criminal Defense Firm Marketing
Leave Your Phone for Callback
